<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quick Guides on Limited Knowledge</title><link>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Quick Guides on Limited Knowledge</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Git</title><link>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/git/</guid><description>Install MacOs brew install git Windows choco install git Configure At minimum, you should set the user name and email address to be associated with your commits.
git config user.name &amp;#34;Full Name&amp;#34; git config user.email &amp;#34;contact@domain.tld&amp;#34; ` Multiple Personas To support multiple personas, create incremental configuration files and import the right one depending on where the repository is in your filesystem.
contents of ~/Code//gitconfig.inc
[user] name = full name email = someone@somewhere.</description></item><item><title>PowerShell</title><link>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/powershell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/powershell/</guid><description>Install MacOs brew tap homebrew/cask-versions brew cask install powershell Windows choco install powershell-core Configure Profile Install the required modules once:
Install-Module posh-git, oh-my-posh -Scope CurrentUser Add the following to your $PROFILE
#Give me $PsLastOutput for when I forget to assign it to something $PSDefaultParameterValues[“Out-Default:OutVariable”] = “PsLastOutput” #Make my shell look pretty Import-Module posh-git Import-Module oh-my-posh Set-Theme Agnoster</description></item><item><title>SSH</title><link>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/ssh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marvtherobot.github.io/reference/docs/guides/ssh/</guid><description>Install MacOs brew install ssh Windows choco install ssh Configure ssh-keygen -t rsa Follow instructions Multiple Personas When providing a host alias, try to retain the original url and provide only suffix.
This can help things like Azure DevOps VsCode extensions to continue to function. ~/.ssh/config Host ssh.dev.azure.com.WORK HostName ssh.dev.azure.com IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa_WORK IdentitiesOnly yes Add host alias entries as required
When cloning Use the Host entry instead of the HostName, the specified key will then be used.</description></item></channel></rss>